WARNA KISHORE FRONT END DEVELOPER

💌 swarnakishoree@gmail.com 🚱 swarnakishore.github.io/Portfolio/ **in** swarnakishore 🗘 SwarnaKishore

SUMMARY

Experience in designing & developing web applications using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and jQuery.

Experience in building web applications using Meteor, a javascript web framework written using Node.js

Experience working on client side using AngularJS, Bootstrap, Material Design, CSS3 Animaton.

Experience in improving performance/responsiveness of web applications.

Experience working with MongoDB, SQL.

Knowledge of object oriented and functional programming.

Experience in using/maintaining GitHub.

All my projects can be viewed in my portfolio website: http://swarnakishore.github.io/Portfolio/.

The code for all the projects is available at my github profile - https://github.com/swarnakishore.

EXPERIENCE

She Can Be - *Developer*

Jul 2014 - Oct 2014

Voluntary work for the nonprofit organisation "SheCanBe" in enhancing and maintaining their websites. Responsibilities include create/modify web pages (using PHP, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Wordpress) for both desktop and mobile devices.

Smart Patient - *User Interface Designer*

May 2013 - Nov 2013

Responsible for designing and developing the web UI, which is built using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.

SKILLS

AngularJS, Meteor, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Material Design, HTML, CSS, C, C++, Photoshop, Apache Web Server, MongoDB, SQL, Git, ASP.NET Web API

PROJECTS

Tutorial Hunt - http://tutorialhunt.herokuapp.com/

A personal project that has been featured on Product Hunt and upvoted by 350+ members. Developed using Meteor, MongoDB and front end using Material Design

Materialize Themes - http://swarnakishore.github.io/MaterializeThemes/

Themes built using a modern responsive front-end framework "Materialize" which is based on "Material Design".

Blast off with bootstrap - http://swarnakishore.github.io/Blast-off-with-bootstrap/

Blast off with Bootstrap is a collection of themes and templates built using Bootstrap framework.

ONLINE PORTFOLIO

Portfolio - http://swarnakishore.github.io/Portfolio/

Github - https://github.com/SwarnaKishore

EDUCATION

Acharya Nagarjuna University, India.

Bachelors Degree in Computer Science with 82% September 2009 to April 2013